Caffè Lena collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Subseries 3: 20th Anniversary (John Nazarenko collection)
    - David Bromberg with guest fiddler, Robin and Linda Williams, May 21, 1980, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, half track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR057)
      Original item ID: 20th B4 0010.
    - David Bromberg with guest fiddler and vocalist, May 21, 1980, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, half track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR058)
      Original item ID: 20th B4 0011.
    - Arlo Guthrie with Shenandoah, May 21, 1980, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, half track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR059)
      Original item ID: 20th B4 0012.
    - Kate and Anna McGarrigle, May 21, 1980, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, half track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR060)
      Original item ID: 20th B4 0013.
  - Subseries 4: Robert Durand's "Caffè Lena Show" (ZBS Media collection)
    - Kenny Hall, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR062)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0002. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1.
    - Balfa Freres, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR063)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0003. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1.
    - Happy and Artie Traum, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR066)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0006. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1.
    - Don McLean, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR067)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0007. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1.
    - Coster, Wailen and Wallach, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR070)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0010. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1. Spelling of surnames is unconfirmed.
    - Gordon Bok, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR071)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0011. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1.
    - David Amram, with Charles Chip, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR076)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0016. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1. David (guitar, vocals, flute, etc.), Charles Chip (guitar and banjo).
    - Dave Van Ronk, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR077)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0017. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1.
    - Jacqui and Bridie, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR078)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0018. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1.
    - Utah Phillips, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR080)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0020. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 1.
    - Roy Bookbinder and Fats Kaplan, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR061)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0001. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Sparky Rucker, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR064)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0004. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Michael Cooney, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR065)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0005. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Sleepy John Estes, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR068)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0008. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Rosalie Sorrels, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR069)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0009. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Central Park Sheiks, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR072)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0012. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Paul Geremia, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR073)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0013. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Frankie Armstrong, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR074)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0014. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Bill Staines, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR075)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0015. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
    - Will S. [Will Scarlett?] and Janis V., circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR079)
      Original item ID: RD ZBS B5 0019. From The Caffè Lena Show (radio broadcast), season 2.
  - Subseries 5: Lena Spencer collection
    Original materials collected by Lena Spencer. SR371-389 donated by Mary Hermance. SR390-397 donated by Peter Davis. SR398-408 donated by Scarlett. SR409-410 donated by Skip Penk's sister. SR411 donated by Ellen Tanner.
    - The McGarrigles with Roma Baron, 1972 (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR411)
      Probably Kate and Anna McGarrigle. Recorded at Caffè Lena.
    - Cranberry Lake Pickin' and Singin' Society, Utah Phillips, Kate Wolf, circa 1972-1973, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR376)
      The group Cranberry Lake Pickin' and Singin' Society later changed their name to Cranberry Lake Jug Band.
    - The Swamp Root String Band, circa 1972-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR081)
      Band members: Steve Slottow (fiddle), Sandy Stark (fiddle), Brian Williams (banjo), Joe Rickard (guitar), Molly Stouten (bass fiddle).
      - Side A: Yellow Cat, Rockingham Cindy, Rocky Road to Dublin (Steve), Whiskey Before Breakfast, Down the Old Plank Road, Drowsy Maggie (Steve, Sandy), circa 1972-1979
      - Side B: Medley: Arkansas Traveler, Western Country, Jaybird, Sally Ann (recorded in concert), Sugar Hill, The Wind that Shakes the Barley (Steve, Sandy)
    - Rosalie Sorrels with Utah Phillips, April 26, 1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR412)
    - Utah Phillips, Barbara Carns, October 31, 1976; November 1976, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR375)
    - Welling and Wallach, Greg Clarke, July 10, 1977; July 2, 1977, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR381)
      Welling and Wallach recorded on July 10; Greg Clarke recorded on July 2.
    - Reels 14-15, side 1 - #10, side 2 - #11, probably 1977, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR396)
      Various artists (Arlo Guthrie and the Shenandoah Band, hosted by Linda and Robin Williams).
    - Jim Ringer and Mary McCaslin; Margaret MacArthur, January 10, 1978; November 6, 1978, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR388)
      Ringer and McCaslin recorded on November 6; MacArthur recorded on November 10.
    - Rosalie Sorrels, George and Vaughn Ward, April 2, 1978; April 1978, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR413)
      Rosalie recorded at Caffè Lena (April 2, 1978). George and Vaughn Ward recorded at 8th Step (April 1978).
    - Jacqui and Bridie, George and Vaughn Ward, April 29, 1978; April 1978, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR379)
      Part or all recorded at Caffè Lena. Recorded on two dates; only one of the dates is known.
    - Robin and Linda Williams; Rosalie Sorrels, September 24, 1978, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR371)
      The year is conjectural.
    - Eric Schoenberg; Jim Ringer and Mary McCaslin, November 3-4, 1978; November 6, 197, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR389)
      Eric Schoenberg recorded on November 3-4 at 8th Step; Ringer and McCaslin recorded November 6 at Caffè Lena.
    - Bob [surname not noted]; Margaret MacArthur; unannounced male musician, November 10, 1978, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR387)
    - Andy Cohen and company, Happy and Artie Traum, January 12, 1979; January 5, 1979, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR414)
    - Andy Cohen, Rosalie Sorrels, January 12, 1979; January 19, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR386)
      Cohen recorded at Caffè Lena on January 12; Sorrels recorded at 8th Step on January 19.
    - Bill Staines, Jean Redpath, February 17-18, 1979, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR385)
      Staines recorded February 17 at 8th Step; Redpath recorded February 18 at Caffè Lena.
    - Jean Redpath, Jeff Cahill and Van Mertz, February 18, 1979; 1979, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR384)
      Not recorded at Caffè Lena.
    - Fox Hollow, Faith Petric, August 15, 1979; August 1979, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR383)
      Fox Hollow recorded on an unidentified date in August 1979 at Caffè Lena. Faith Petric recorded on August 15 at Caffè Lena.
    - Faith Petric, Greg Clarke, August 1979; August 15, 1979, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR382)
      Faith Petric recorded on August 15 at Caffè Lena; Greg Clarke recorded on an unidentified date in August at Caffè Lena.
    - Utah Phillips and Rosalie Sorrels, Greg Clarke, August 1979; August 15, 1979, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR374)
    - Frankie Armstrong, July 2, 1980; July 3, 1980, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR372)
    - Frankie Armstrong, July 5, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR373)
    - Lena Spencer sings original songs (1 of 2), February 21, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR082)
    - Lena Spencer sings original songs (2 of 2), February 21, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR083)
      See note for SR083.
    - Lena's Open Door (radio show), June 23, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR085)
    - Rick Danko, February 6, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR400)
    - Rick Danko (1 of 2), September 17, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR398)
    - Rick Danko (2 of 2), September 17, 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR399)
    - Peter Rowan (1 of 2), November 13, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR404)
    - Peter Rowan (2 of 2), November 13, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR405)
    - Membership, reels 16-17 (#8); side 2 - #8, side 1 - #9, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR390)
      Unannounced artists live at an unidentified venue (not Caffè Lena), for a tribute/benefit for Lena. Includes Kate and Anna McGarrigle.
    - Open Mic show (WKAJ): interview with Lena Spencer, August 28, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR086)
    - Freeze Guillory and the Bon Temps Zydeco Band (1 of 2), May 31, 1990, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR402)
    - Freeze Guillory and the Bon Temps Zydeco Band (2 of 2), May 31, 1990, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR403)
    - Rory Block, June 2, 1990, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR406)
    - Mystery Ranch, May 12, 1991, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR401)
    - The Bird Sisters (1 of 2), November 24, 1992, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR407)
    - The Bird Sisters (2 of 2), November 24, 1992, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR408)
    - Skip Penk live at Caffè Lena, December 11, 1992, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR410)
    - Rosalie Sorrels and Paul Geremia, January 1, 1993, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR474)
    - Skip Penk live at Caffè Lena, September 13, 1997, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR409)
    - Lena Spencer sings over a sequenced instrumental followed by episodes of her radio show, "Saratoga Springs", 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR084)
    - Jacqui and Bridie, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR377)
    - Jacqui and Bridie, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR378)
      SR377 and SR378 may be recordings from one concert.
    - Coster, Welling and Wallach, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR380)
    - Schooner Fare (DAT 7); Gamble Rogers (DAT 8), 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR391)
    - Various artists (DAT 13); June Tabor/Mark Emerson (DAT 14), 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR392)
    - Reels 18-19, #6, #7, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR393)
    - Reels 22-23, side 2 - #2, side 1 - #3, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR394)
      Bill Staines, announced artists; Robin and Linda Williams, hosts; live at a venue other than Caffè Lena; a benefit for Lena Spencer and Caffè Lena.
    - Reels 20-21, side 1 - #5, side 2 - #4, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR395)
      Nick Seeger, Michael Kuni, unannounced artists; live at a venue other than Caffè Lena; a benefit for Lena Spencer and Caffè Lena.
    - Gamble Rogers (DAT 8); Steve Gillette/Cindy Mangsen (DAT 9), 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR397)
    - Pete Seeger interview [?], 1 sound microcassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR473)
  - Subseries 6: Caffè Lena History Project collection
    - Bill Faier live at Caffè Lena, May 6, 1967, 1 sound disc (CD-R): digital, two track, mono. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR531)
      Original reel recording housed in Billy Faier Collection held by Southern Folklife Collection,
    - Frankie Armstrong and Fox Hollow, Jacqui and Bridie, April 11, 1964; December 1, 1974 (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR097)
      Frankie Armstrong and Fox Hollow recorded in 1964; Jacqui and Bridie recorded in 1974. Side B is blank.
    - Bound for Glory, Sesame Street, Enormous Room, and possibly other recordings, February 14, 1971; March 5, 1971; March 27, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR094)
      May not all be recorded at Caffè Lena.
    - The McGarrigles [Kate and Anna McGarrigle], August 23, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 3 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR088)
      Engineer notes that the recording may be a pre-show or post-show recording, possibly a demo of songs.
    - Enormous Room, Bill Staines, Bottle Hill, 666, March 27, 1972; May 7, 1972; May 27, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR096)
      The recording of 666 is unconfirmed.
    - Hedy West, 666, June 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR095)
    - Heatherwood, Rosalie Sorrels, July 3, 1972; July 23, 1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR098)
    - Rosalie Sorrels, Fox Hollow, August 23, 1972; July 21, 1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR091)
    - Coster, Welling and Wallach, Tom McCreesh (1 of 3), January 18, 1974; June 16, 1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR100)
    - Coster, Welling and Wallach, Tom McCreesh (2 of 3), January 18, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR101)
    - Coster, Welling and Wallach (3 of 3), and possibly other artists, January 19, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR099)
    - The McGarrigles w/ Roma Baron, and possibly other artists, May 26, 1974; June 9, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR093)
    - The McGarrigles with Roma Baron, Frankie Armstrong, June 9, 1974; July 28, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR092)
    - Rosalie Sorrels, Donna DeChristopher, October 13, 1974; October 26, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR090)
    - Rosalie Sorrels, Joe Hickerson, April 26, 1975; May 4, 1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR089)
    - Rosalie Sorrels (1 of 2), April 2, 1978, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR475)
      Side B described as broken. Original item ID: B7 0022.
    - Rosalie Sorrels (2 of 2), April 2, 1978, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR476)
      Tape described as broken. Original item ID: B7 0023.
    - Billy Brislane; Armstrong, Garvey and Mitchell, November 25-26, 1978, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR104)
      Billy Brislane recorded on November 25 at 8th Step; Armstrong, Mitchell and Garvey recorded on November 26 at Caffè Lena.
    - Armstrong, Mitchell, and Garvey; Mike Cross, November 26, 1978, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR103)
    - Don Armstrong and Victoria Garvey, Mike Cross, December 9, 1978; undated, 1 sound cassette (120 min.): analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR102)
    - Don McLean: tape broadcast on WRPI of 14th Caffè Lena appearance, circa 1970-1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR087)
    - Michael Cooney, set I, September 9, 1989, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR477)
    - Michael Cooney, set II, September 9, 1989, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR478)
  - Subseries 7: Dick Kavanaugh collection
    - Sub-subseries 1: Music
      - Oscar Brand on radio WSPN "Lena's Open Door," February 14, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR269)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0014.
      - Margaret MacArthur (1 of 2), March 20, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR186)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0043.
      - Margaret MacArthur (2 of 2), March 20, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR187)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0044. Side B is blank.
      - Phil Cooper and Margaret Nelson live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), March 27, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR288)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0033.
      - Phil Cooper and Margaret Nelson live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), March 27, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR289)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0034. Side B is blank.
      - Peppino D'Agostino live at Caffè Lena, March 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR296)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0041. The engineer's notes indicate the recording date was May 2, 1987.
      - The Fuzzy Brothers live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), March 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR297)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0042. The engineer's notes indicate the recording date was May 8, 1987.
      - The Fuzzy Brothers live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), March 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR298)
        Side B is blank. Original item ID: DK B5 0043. The engineer's notes indicate the recording date was May 8, 1987.
      - Utah Phillips (1 of 3), April 4, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR204)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0006.
      - Utah Phillips (2 of 3), April 4, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR205)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0007.
      - Utah Phillips (3 of 3), April 4, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR206)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0008.
      - Addie and Olin, April 4, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR330)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0016.
      - New Performer Showcase: Dave Utter, Nick DeBellis, Addie and Olin, Virginia Leonard (storyteller) (1 of 2), April 12, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR346)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0033.
      - New Performer Showcase: Dave Utter, Nick DeBellis, Addie and Olin, Virginia Leonard (storyteller) (2 of 2), April 12, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR347)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0034.
      - Steve Gillette live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), April 17, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR293)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0038.
      - Steve Gillette live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), April 17, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR294)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0039. Side B is blank.
      - Lena's graduation party (1 of 2), May 10, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR231)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0033.
      - Lena's graduation party (2 of 2), May 10, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR230)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0032.
      - Aztec Two-Step (1 of 2), May 15, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR180)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0037.
      - Aztec Two-Step (2 of 2), May 15, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR181)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0038. Side B is blank.
      - New Performer Showcase: Kevin Rowe, Ebie Brown, Marcie Lee Cutting, Dave Debonzo, May 31, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR343)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0029.
      - Bill Staines live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), June 12, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR303)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0048.
      - Bill Staines live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), June 12, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR304)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0049.
      - Tom Mitchell's farewell performance live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), June 19, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR307)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0052.
      - Tom Mitchell's farewell performance live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), June 19, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR308)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0053. Side B is blank.
      - Paul Geremia (1 of 2), July 3, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR317)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0003.
      - Paul Geremia (2 of 2), July 3, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR318)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0004.